# Write your code below this line ðŸ‘‡
question_data = [
    {"question": "A slugs blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Approximately one quarter of the human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The total surface area of human lungs is the size of the football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In West Virginia, ISA, if you accidently hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the house of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "It is illegal to pee in the ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
];